Contact

8324449277 (Home) amberferro@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amber-ferro-295a3322 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hospitals
Critical Care
Healthcare Management

Amber Ferro

Nurse Manager Houston Northwest Medical Center Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Unit Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Critical Care, Cardio-Thoracic care, Stroke, Medical-Surgical, and Telemetry. Strong leadership skills with a Master's degree focused in Nursing Administration.

Experience

Houston Northwest Medical Center 13 years 1 month

Med-Surg/Telemetry, Intermediate Unit Manager July 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month) Houston, Texas

Cardiovascular Surgery and Neurosiences Coordinator July 2014 - July 2016 (2 years 1 month) Houston, Texas

Rapid Response Team
July 2007 - September 2014 (7 years 3 months)

HNMC -Surgical Intensive Care RN July 2001 - July 2007 (6 years 1 month)

Education

Aspen University

Master's degree, Nursing Administration · (2015 - 2017)

Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi Bachelors, Nursing · (1998 - 2000)

Blinn College

Associate of Science (A.S.), Biology, General · (1995 - 1998)